Preliminary Guide to the Special Collections Department, Gelman Library records, 1819-2014 RG0110
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Exhibits, 1935-2010; RG0110 Series 5; 8.25 Linear Feet
  - 1996 (November 4 1996 - February 28 1997) Inaugural Celebrations in the Nation's Capital Symposium Programs, 4 November 1996 - 28 February 1997; RG 0110 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1996 (April 15 - October 18) Washington DC Then and Now: The Photographic Legacy of Charles Suddarth Kelly, 15 April - 18 October 1996; RG 0110 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 1997 (January 14 - February 21) Exhibit: A Creative Hand c. Francine Henderson, 14 January - 21 February 1997; RG 0110 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 1997 (April 7 - June 24) "Contemporary British Authors", 7 April - 24 June 1997; RG 0110 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 1997 (July 10 - August 15) Living Art Through 25 Years, 10 July - 15 August 1997; RG 0110 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 1997 (July 10 - August 15) Living Art Through 25 years, 10 July - 15 August 1997; RG 0110 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 1997 (October 18) "History Fair", Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1997 (September 4 - November 21) "Queerly Visible: The Work of JEB (Joan E. Biren)", Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 1998 (March 14 -July 10) "City of Magnificent Illusions", Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1998 (August 28 - October 28) "March on Washington", Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1998 (August 28 - October 28) "March on Washington", Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 1998 (April 26) Celebration of Lusk Donation, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1999 (March 10 - December 30) "Goodbye, Comrade.. .", Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 1999 (March 10 - December 30) "Goodbye Comrade.. ." Curator La Nina Clayton, Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1999 Goodbye Comrade, Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 2000 (February 1 - May 1) "Africana Women Curator: Francine Henderson, Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 2000 "Bright Stars Through the Perilous Fight': Men and Women Who Would Be President Curator: Burnadette A. Boucher, Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 2000 (June - September) Home Base: The Neighborhoods of Washington, DC, Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 2001 (26 April - 21 December) "Shall We Dance...?", 26 April - 21 December 2001; RG 0110 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 2002 (October 21 - December 20) "Of a Dubious Nature": Banned and Challenged Books, 21 October - 20 December 2002; RG 0110 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 2003 (January 21 - June 30) "The President's Physician: The Life and Legacy of Dr. Janet G. Travell" (University Archives), 21 January - 30 June 2003; RG 0110 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 2003 Capitol Hill Restoration Society Exhibit, RG 0110 Series 5 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Exhibits - Photographs and Negatives, 14 June 1993 - 16 June 1994; Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Exhibit titles include:
    Our Disappearing Art Heritage Charting Religious Horizions, Holy Land Maps from the Halperin Collection Students Passions, The Fine Art of Collecting Permanent Residents: Cemetery Memorials of 19th Century Washingtonians
  - Exhibits - Photographs and Negatives, September 1994 - 28 June 1995; Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Treasures from the Collection Friendship House Celebrating the Wonderful World of Charles Dickens City Invincible: Walt Whitman's Washington From Plantagenet to Saxe-Coburg: Maps from the Fiat Lux Library 1482-1899
  - Exhibits - Photographs and Negatives, 6 October 1995 - 21 March 1996; Series 5 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Capital Commitment: The Committee of 100 on the Federal City Lost in the City: An African-American Perspective of the Nation's Capital. Exhibit and Symposium. Gratefully Yours...175 Years of Library Gifts Our Other Lives Sonneck Society
  - Exhibits - Photographs and Negatives, October 1996 - 10 July 1997; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Subjects include:
    Video Free Earth event Inaugural Celebrations, exhibit and symposium Creative Hands Valerie Lester's poetry class British Fiction at the Millennium - Alan Cheuse, Michael Dirda, Margaret Soltan, Susan Willens City of Magnificent Illusions, D.C. Fiction Living Art Through Twenty-Five Years
  - Exhibits - Photographs and Negatives, 20 February 1998 - 26 April 2001; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Association of Research Libraries (ARL) tour of Special Collections Joan Biren Faculty Author's Reception March on Washington Goodbye Comrade Shaw Home Base exhibit Shall We Dance exhibit
  - Exhibits - Photographs and Negatives, undated; Series 5 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    A Chesapeake Product: The Early History of Tobacco Foggy Bottom: History of a Neighborhood
  - Museum, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Index to exhibit files, undated; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Publicity Materials, 1997-2008; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Publicity Materials, 2000-2011; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Publicity Materials, 2000-2010; Series 5 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Exhibit, 1999; RG0110 Series 6; .25 Linear feet (Map-folder 1)
  This series includes two posters and catalogs from the Goodbye Comrade exhibit from 1999.
  Formerly ACC#746
- Slides, RG0110 Series 7; .25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes 143 slides on the history of GW libraries.
  Formerly ACC#874
- Public programming, RG0110 Series 8; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Folder 1)
  This series contains slides. 37 slides on the history of cheerleading and 33 slides on the history of the Elliott School of International Affairs.
  Formerly ACC#875 and ACC#876
- Photographs and posters, RG0110 Series 9; 2.25 Linear feet (Map-folder 2, Map-folder 1, Flat box 1, Flat box 2)
  This series includes photographs and posters from exhibits for 20th and 25th anniversaries of the Gelman Library.
  Formerly ACC#933
  - Gelman Library 20th Anniversary Poster, 1993
  - blueprint of Special Collections space in Gelman (2nd floor), undated; Series 9 (Map-folder 2)
- Faculty publications, 1964-1997; RG0110 Series 10; 3 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series contains bibliographies of faculty publications including the medical and law schools. These records date from 1964-97.
  Formerly ACC#1063
  - Article listing, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Rubberbanded together in folder
  - Medical School Departmental Publications, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Bound volume, loose in box
  - Medical School Departmental Publications, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Medical School Departmental Publications, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Medical School Departmental Publications, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Medical School Departmental Publications, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Medical School Departmental Publications, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Medical School Departmental Publications, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Medical School Departmental Publications, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Medical School Faculty Bibliography, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bibliography of Faculty Publications, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bibliography of Faculty Publications [1/2], 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bibliography of Faculty Publications [2/2], 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bibliography of Faculty Publications, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Black bound volume, loose in box
  - Bibliography of Faculty Publications, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    In manilla folder
  - School of Government and Business Administration Research Index [1/2], 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - School of Government and Business Administration Research Index [2/2], 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Publications of the Faculty of the George Washington University Medical Center, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Publication listings by department - Accountancy Department, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Blue folders
  - Publication listings by department - American Studies, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Publication listings by department - Department of Anesthesiology, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Publication listings by department - Anatomy, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Publication listings by department - Department of Biochemistry, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Publication listings by department - Biological Sciences, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Publication listings by department - Biostatistics, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Publication listings by department - Business Administration, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Publication listings by department - Department of Chemistry, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Publication listings by department - Child Health Development, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Publication listings by department - Civil, Mechanical and Environmental Engineering, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Publication listings by department - Computer Medicine, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Publication listings by department - Dermatology, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Publication listings by department - Electrical Engineering and Computer Sciences, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Publication listings by department - Engineering, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Publication listings by department - Engineering Administration, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Publication listings by department - Department of English, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Publication listings by department - Health Care Service, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Publication listings by department - History, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Publication listings by department - Department of Management Science, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Publication listings by department - Medicine, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Publication listings by department - Department of Orthopaedic Surgery, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Publication listings by department - Department of Physiology, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Publication listings by department - Pathology, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Publication listings by department - Pharmacology, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Publication listings by department - Department of Philosophy, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Publication listings by department - Political Science, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Publication listings by department - Department of Psychiatry, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Publication listings by department - Department of Public Administration, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Publication listings by department - Department of Radiology, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Publication listings by department - Statistics, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Publication listings by department - Urban and Regional Plannin, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - School of Government and Business Administration Research Index [1/2], 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - School of Government and Business Administration Research Index [2/2], 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - School of Government and Business Administration Cumulative Research Abstracts, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Publications of the Faculty of the George Washington University Medical Center [1/2], 1986 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Publications of the Faculty of the George Washington University Medical Center [2/2], 1986 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - School of Government and Business Administration Research Index, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Publications of the Faculty of the George Washington University Medical Center (preliminary draft), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - School of Government and Business Administration Research Index, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - School of Government and Business Administration Cumulative Research Abstracts, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Jacob Burns Law Library Faculty Publications, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Publications of the Faculty of the George Washington University Medical Center, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Publications of the Faculty of the George Washington University Medical Center, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Publications of the Faculty of the George Washington University Medical Center, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Publication lists (various departments), correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - National Law Center Faculty Publications, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Publications of the George Washington University Medical Center, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Publications of the George Washington University Medical Center, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Annual GW Faculty Authors Exhibition, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    In folder
  - The George Washington University Faculty Authors' Publications [1/2], 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The George Washington University Faculty Authors' Publications [2/2], 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Publications of the George Washington University Medical Center, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The George Washington University Faculty Author Publications [1/2], 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The George Washington University Faculty Author Publications [2/2], 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The George Washington University Faculty Author Publications [1/2], 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The George Washington University Faculty Author Publications [2/2], 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Publications of the Faculty of the George Washington University Medical Center, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The George Washington University Faculty Publications [1/2], 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The George Washington University Faculty Publications [2/2], 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Jacob Burns School of Law Faculty Publications, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Publications of the George Washington University Medical Center, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Publications of the George Washington University Medical Center, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Photographs, George Washington University and WWII Exhibit, 1940-1999; RG0110 Series 11; 3.5 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 3, Box 1)
  This series includes photographs and print materials used in exhibits on George Washington University and World War II, including student scenes, campus activities, Alleghany proving grounds, veterans, buildings, Materials in this series date from 1940-1947.
  Formerly ACC#1025
  - First Aid training, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hatchet staff sitting around table, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Girl selling war stamps, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Found in 1943 Cherry Tree, p. 37
  - Bassin's GW Inn restaurant, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Griffith Stadium, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Students standing on steps outside Strong Hall, 1940ca. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Girl selling war stamps, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Note: same as #3
  - Women in uniform outside a GW building, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Portrait of men with baseball bats & gloves, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Women playing badminton in GW inn, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Group shot of ROTC members, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Football game, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Homecoming queen pageant, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Students in line for class registration, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Campus radio station in Lisner auditorium, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Two basketball players and a cheerleader walking down the sidewalk, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Students outside the Student Union building, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bell Hall and Stuart Hall from G. St., 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Woman student standing outside Lisner Auditorium at night, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Students standing outside Lisner Auditorium at night, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Collage of GW student activities, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Man lecturing to students in classroom, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Collage of campus buildings, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Students listening to lecture, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Five women doing first aid training, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Veterans standing outside Veteran's Club at 722 22nd St., 07/27/1944 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Note: from summer school record-GW Hatchet
  - Veteran dormitories, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - People playing a card game, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Collage of campus activities, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Note: from 1940 Cherry Tree, p. 82
  - Collage of campus activities, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Note: from 1942 Cherry Tree, p. 10
  - Students at vegetable market, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - People sitting around tables eating dinner outside, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Students sitting in the University Yard, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Elmer Kayser and un-identified man with Bill Reinhart signing contract, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Collage of campus activities, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Note: from 1946 Cherry Tree
  - Men and women partying, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Note: from 1944 Cherry Tree
  - Students working on an edition of the Hatchet, 1945ca. (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Students listening to a lecture, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Red Auerbach, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Note: from 1940 Cherry Tree
  - Collage of campus scenes, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Note from 1947 Cherry Tree
  - Elmer Kayser lecturing in Lisner Auditorium, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Note: 8 x 10
  - Elmer Kayser lecturing in Lisner Auditorium, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Note: 16 x 20
  - Veteran playing ball with young son, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Veteran playing ball with young son, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Margaret Truman and Jane Lingo studying, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Margaret Truman and Jane Lingo studying, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Note 16 x 20
  - Men with flame thrower at Allegheny proving grounds, 1945ca. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Note: managed by GWU
  - Man with bazooka at Allegheny proving grounds, 1945ca. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Women standing at dock watching ship come in, 1945ca. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Students studying in library, 1945ca. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - President Cloyd Heck Marvin with group of veterans, 1945ca. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Rockets attached to airplane wing, 1945ca. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hatchet reporter with man looking at flame thrower at Allegheny proving grounds, 1945ca. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Washington conference on theoretical physics, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Collage of student activities, 1945ca. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Collage of campus activities, 1945ca. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Three men at homecoming rally with "Royal Blue Express" train, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - American Veterans Committee magazine (AVC), newsletter "AVC Courier", and program, 1945ca. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Labels from WWII exhibit, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Life magazine, 03/10/1941 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Photocopies of various pictures for and about WWII exhibit, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Various papers, 3 photos, "Summer School Record" newspaper, 1944ca. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Transcripts, papers, correspondence, 1935-1999; RG0110 Series 12; 5.5 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 4, Box 1, Box 2)
  This series includes oral history transcripts, photocopies of books, articles, papers, correspondence, notes, and photos. These materials are concerning George Gamow and theoretical physics, including materials and videotapes from the April 12, 1996 symposium at GW. They range in date from 1935-1999.
  Formerly ACC#1026
  This series has a paper container list in the reading room, please ask staff for assistance.
- Exhibits and collections, 1976-2010; RG0110 Series 13; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains memorandums, invitation, brochures, a calendar, programs, a certificate, an organization chart, reports, inventiveness, flyers, newspaper articles, photographs, and a press release. They range in date from 1976 to 2010. The materials cover collections, achievements, goals, recommendations, exhibits, and the Kiev room.
  Formerly vertical files
  - Library, University - Special Collections, 07/09/1975-05/2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Library, University - Special Collections exhibits, 05/16/1976-2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Library, University - Special Collections Kiev Room, 10/30/1996-04/24/2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Exhibition - "Turning Wood into Art: A Gift from Jane and Arthur Mason to the Gelman Library" - Opening Reception, 2006 October 20; RG0110 Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Contains photographs, a postcard, and a brochure.
  - Pages from the Field: The Andrew Oliver Book Collection for Classical and Near Easter Studies, 14 April 2010 - 15 June 1020; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    This file contains 1 DVD with images of the exhibition, 1 event invitation, 1 event program, and 1 exhibit brochure.
- Janet G. Travell exhibit, 2003; RG0110 Series 14; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of of photographs, photocopy reproductions, a videotape, and labels. The exhibit titled "The President's Physician: The Life And Legacy Of Dr. Janet G. Travell" was displayed in Gelman Library's Special Collections Department from January-August 2003. The videotape was of an exhibit program with Henry Fishman, Lawrence Funt, Robert Gerwin, and Nancy Shaw sharing memories of Dr. Travell. The reproductions included an article from Texas Heart Institute Journal titled "Janet G. Travell, MD: A Daughter's Recollection."
  - Labels for The President's Physician: The Life and Legacy of Dr. Janet G. Travell, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - News release and exhibit guide, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Videotape of an exhibit program with Henry Fishman, Lawrence Funt, Robert Gerwin, and Nancy Shaw sharing memories of Dr. Travell, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Attendees and comment pages from exhibit guest book, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Article from Texas Heart Institute Journal - "Janet G. Travell, MD: A Daughter's Recollection" by Virginia Wilson, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Duplicate materials from Travell papers that may be used in exhibits, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Photo reproduction of Dr. Travell, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Includes negative
  - Scanned reproduction of Dr. Travell and sister in 1908, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    From office hours
  - Photo reproduction of Dr. Travell's mother, Janet Davidson, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Scanned reproduction of Dr. Travell by electric ambulance, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Photocopy of newspaper clipping of Dr. Travell's engagement, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Scanned reproduction of Dr. Travell on her wedding day, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Photocopy of newspaper clipping of Dr. Travell and husband on wedding day, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photo reproduction of Dr. Travell at Sports Award Buffet, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    From Acc#133, folder 490; with negative
  - Photocopy of Dr. Travell at Japanese Embassy, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Scanned reproduction of Dr. Travell as a baby with her mother holding her, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Photo reproduction of the Travell family, includes Dr. Travell, husband, daughter, son-in-law, and grandchildren, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Scanned reproduction of Dr. Travell's father, Willard Travell, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Photo reproduction of John Powell on JFK's Inauguration Day, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Scanned reproduction of Dr. Travell holding her baby daughter, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Scanned reproduction of Dr. Travell and husband driving in car, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dr. Travell's baby book and scanned reproduction of one page, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Photocopy of page from Dr. Travell's report card for month of February, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Photo reproduction of New York Hospital, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Photo reproduction of Dr. Travell, ambulance surgeon, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Scanned reproduction of Dr. Travell and sister at Wellesley College-Tennis Doubles Champions, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Photocopy of tennis list with Dr. Travell's name, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Photo reproduction of Dr. Travell coming across a cable line, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Photo reproduction of Dr. Travell sitting on a high perch, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)